You took Aira from me!
My little Aira!
Give her back!
You filthy pigs!
Aira-chan is getting in our way.
What a downer.
What should we do, Momo-chan?
Just keep running away!
This place is full of obstacles.
I can't run fast.
It's fine! I have an idea!
You're not getting away!
You delinquent girl!
Momo-chan!
Give Aira back!
You dimwit wiener boy!
Makes me wilt.
In this tricky terrain...
you're trying to escape my acrobatics?
Of course you can't!
It's fine, Aira.
If you don't want to say
"Mommy" that much,
I'm okay with that.
I just want to be together with you.
By devouring you,
you'll become my flesh and blood.
Then that way, I can be with you forever!
So let me properly...
masticate you.
What is this? What is going on?
Why can't I move forward?
Your acrobatics ensnare
anything and everything, right?
With that singed granny perm you've got,
it looks like you can't let go
of the things you ensnare.
Nice, Okarun!
You ran away really well!
Damn pigs!
Don't you think
you've caught me with this trick!
Miss Ayase! She's trying to break
the beams to free herself!
Like I'd let you!
Don't you dare touch my beautiful legs,
you punk delinquent girl!
Okarun, go at full throttle!
You haven't done it yet, right?
Go full throttle and blow her away!
Blow her away? How do I do that?
Huh?
When we fought the alien,
I was flustered and a bit desperate.
And with the location-bound spirit,
I was devoting myself to fleeing!
I have never properly
blown a person away!
Why are you telling me now
after all this? Just kick her away!
Kick her away, like in soccer?
Like I'd know!
I don't care what, just do it quick!
Not good! Hurry, Okarun!
I can't hold her back anymore!
You little punks...
I'll kill you!
Okarun, send her flying!
Wicked.
The hell?
Full throttle is amazing! Okarun, you get
things done when you try!
That hurt!
My entire body will explode!
You used my power but this
was all your attack could do?
This is tough.
You son of a bitch!
What should we do with her?
Should we have Grandma exorcise her?
Leave that nobody alone.
It just ate one of my attacks.
She won't be able to use
her spiritual power for a while.
Anyway, the golden ball.
That girl has it, right?
Oh, that's right!
Let's take it while we can.
More like, I really want these zip ties
off my wrists.
Okarun, got a pair of scissors?
I'm sorry, I don't have one.
I've been tied up this whole time
because of this stupid girl.
How is she related
to that Acro-Silky, anyway?
Hey, Momo.
Found the golden ball?
Found it.
Whoa!
Good for you, Okarun!
We found one of your family jewels!
How you say it is so embarrassing.
But more importantly...
What's wrong?
This girl's dead.
Dead?
EPISODE 7
TO A KINDER WORLD
No way!
Okarun, check her pulse!
O-Okay!
It can't be...
An ordinary human
eaten by a yokai will die.
It's nothing to be surprised about.
It just happened
that someone with psychic powers
and someone with my spiritual powers
were spared.
That's all it is.
Okarun, can you do CPR?
Huh? I'm not too confident.
I'll try cardiac massage!
If I use psychic powers,
I can directly massage her heart!
If she's dead, the heart
is nothing more than a chunk of flesh.
One, two, three, four, five...
There's no use in massaging it.
Shut up!
If you're gonna get in our way,
get outta here!
Okarun, breathe!
H-Here goes!
Granny, call an ambulance!
You have Muko's phone, don't you?
Such futility.
Once more!
One, two, three, four, five... Okarun!
One, two, three, four, five...
Aira...
My little Aira...
Damn you!
We don't have time for that!
I'll take care of her! Miss Ayase,
continue with the resuscitation!
Doing that will not bring Aira back to life.
There's a better way.
Give my aura to Aira.
Aura is like a battery for organisms.
Motors don't move without batteries, yes?
Aira's aura is almost gone.
You can augment it with my own.
Who the hell is gonna believe what you say!?
You're just thinking about
eating her again, aren't you!?
And now, I can't eat people anymore.
If you still can't trust me, then you can
crush my head with this steel beam.
What she's saying is true.
Without an aura,
that girl will stay that way.
I don't trust you!
So if you make any funny movements,
I'll instantly crush your head in!
Okarun, you can go full throttle
one more time, right?
Keep her targeted.
You said your were going to augment
this stupid girl's aura with your own.
How do you do that? Tell me.
Use your psychic power to connect my aura
to Aira's dimming aura.
You could say it's like
a communication cable.
Okarun, make sure to keep
your eyes on her.
What a bother.
Here goes!
Let's go to karaoke, like, seriously.
What? Like, we're totally not going.
I'm home.
Don't underestimate us, damn it.
You bitch!
Damn it, what the hell!?
Mommy, thank you for all you do.
I can't remember.
I think I lost something dear to me.
Mommy.
Huh?
You're not her...
Aira!
I told you not to go running off
on your own.
I thought Mommy was there.
There's no way she's around here.
Daddy, where did Mommy go?
I told you many times already.
She's gone to a place very far away.
When will she be back?
She won't be coming back for a while.
That's why, Aira, you have to be stronger.
So that you can do everything on your own
even without Mommy.
So that one day, when Mommy comes back,
she can be proud of what you can do.
Okay! Aira will be a girl
who she can really be proud of!
Child...
Where is... my child?
Aira...
That's right...
I remember now.
I was Aira's...
Mommy.
I will protect her.
So that nobody harms her...
I will...
She came back to life!
Momo-chan, what's wrong?
What did she do to you?
I can take her down
if she does something weird, right?
I'll go full throttle.
Wait!
Stop... Please...
I'm sorry, Aira...
I swore that I would protect you...
but what I did was hurt you.
I can't even control my own emotions.
I have turned into a monster.
So I will end it all now.
Hey! She keeps falling apart.
What's gonna happen to her?
I told you. Aura is like a battery.
Without it, you perish.
And she's leaving regrets behind.
She won't be able to rest in peace.
What will happen, then?
That's pretty much a given.
The void. Nothing will be left of her.
It'll be like she never existed in any world.
The living and the dead...
Everyone will forget about her.
Well, I'm sure her life
was worthless anyway.
Losing the existence
of someone like her ain't much.
It shouldn't be like that.
It's too cruel!
Isn't there something?
Something to let her rest in peace?
Nothing. Whether or not she can
rest in peace is up to her heart.
There's nothing strangers can do.
I wish I could've
bought you more lovely clothing.
played with you a lot more.
More... properly... more...
If you weren't born as my child...
You would have been
so much more happier...
I made you so unfortunate...
I'm so sorry...
Mommy.
I love you.
I was the happiest person in the universe.
Please, so that nobody ever hurts them...
take them to a more fortunate,
kinder world.
I won't forget. I swear.
Momo, you're home?
Yeah. We found a ball,
but only one of them.
I see.
Grandma, I'm hungry.
Wanna eat somen?
That sounds great!
EPISODE 8
I'VE GOT THIS FUNNY FEELING
Next episode,
"I've Got This Funny Feeling."
Looks like I ran out of soup base.
Guess I'll go buy some.